# Jheng-Hao Lin

07784-599601 / hello.linuk@gmail.com / www.linuk.co.uk / Github: linuk / Linked: linuk

#### **Profile**

A technology enthusiast with two web development internship experiences and two years working experience in creative domain industry as a freelancer and company co-founder. Now pursuing the computer science degree out of passion and enthusiasm for technology. Praised for the ability to plan and lead a development project and manage the heavy workload. Possess recognized skills in problem-solving between employers and lecturers at University. Looking for an IT company where I can start my software developer career and showcase my talents.

# **Education**

#### BSc Computer Science, Goldsmiths, University of London

Sept 2016 - Present

- Expected Grade: First Class (Honours). First-year modules average: 91.2% (GPA: 4.0)
- 81% for the Introduction to Programming module with a Mario game project written in Javascript.
- 87% for the Web Development module included a personal project written in React JS.
- 97% for the Problem Solving for Computer Science module related to algorithms in Python.
- iLost project: led a group of 7 people to develop a lost item solution in React Native.

## **Technical Skills**

TypeScript | Javascript | Jest | React | MySQL | Python | Java | PHP | PHPUnit | TDD | Node | ESLint | TSLint | Gulp | Git | jQuery | HTML5 | CSS3 | SASS | Twig | Bootstrap | Gitlab | Github | Symfony | Bulma | Sketch

# Relevant Work Experience

P/T Web Developer - Fashion Kanvas, London

Jan 2017 - Present

- Worked in agile scrum development methodology and developed a web application.
- Communicated with the UX designer and translated user interface designs into React components.
- Built reusable UI components and integrated Firebase APIs with them.

Intern Web Developer - Fiedler AMS s.r.o., The Czech Republic

May 2017 - Sept 2017

- Estimated the developing time period and schedule for 3-month log development process, then followed the plan and recorded the developing progress and reported to supervisor regularly and proactively.
- Designed a new schema, migrated the data from original Drupal database and converted the data to the desired format with Python, then inserted into MySQL
- Developed a fully functional responsive website in Symfony2 from scratch.
- Designed and documented RESTful APIs and developed a customised CMS based on it.
- Created customised CMS application for the website which included a REST API Node server and a SPA built in React, Typescript and used Bulma as the main CSS theme.
- Followed test-driven test standard to write unit tests with PHPUnit for Symfony2 and Jest for Node server.
- Used linters to ensure the consistency of code style and quality. and followed Airbnb Javascript style guide.
- Documented project structure and data flow in Gitlab wiki for future maintenance.

P/T Intern Front-end Web Developer - YesWeStock, London

March 2017 - May 2017

- Converted Sketch into a hand-coded fully responsive website based on industry standard.
- Evaluated the feasibility of the new features and implemented them within a limited time in a calm manner.
- Worked closely with a back-end developer to develop functional and aesthetic web components.
- Proactively improved the user experience of the website by retouching the original logo, colour scheme and user interface of the web application.
- Re-designed the original logo, colour scheme, and the original website with Sketch.

# **Other Work Experience**

**Student Ambassador** - Goldsmiths, University of London

Oct 2016 - Present

- Supported events with other ambassadors as a team to deliver excellent customer service.
- Representative of the computing department at Goldsmiths for sharing university experiences with prospective students.
- Provided desktop support and replied to course queries at the International Office help desk.
- Led tours around the University campus, facility and accommodation for parents and prospective students.

**Volunteer Tutor** - MyCompleteFocus CIC, London

Nov 2016 - Apr 2017

- Mentored and explained programming terms such as variables and loop in easy-to-understand terms that elementary school children can understand.
- Cooperated with club organisers and volunteers to manage the Coding Clubs courses.

#### Freelance Event Photographer - Taiwan

Nov 2014 - Aug 2016

- Negotiated with clients in a positive manner and resolved problems proactively during the events.
- Built partnerships with other local and regional agencies and provided good customer service.
- Responsible attitude targeted at ensuring completion of every project in a time-efficient manner.
- Increased customer base and photographed over 100 events for global brands during the first half year, brands included Ogilvy & Mather, SWAROVSKI, UBS, Nespresso, COVA, Grand Hyatt Taipei and so on.

Co-founder - Magicism. Inc, Taiwan

Sept 2014 - Jan 2016

- Initiated and coordinated advertising campaigns and promotional activities.
- Utilised interpersonal skills when liaising and maintaining relationships with contact person at agencies.
- Presented proposals and co-hosted events via improved communication skill with global brands such as Louis Vuitton, Chopard S.T. Dupont, Chanel, and so on.
- Addressed and fulfilled clients special requirements within the limited time in calm and capable manner.

### **Hackathon Awards**

#### Project Intergate - Third Prize in Hatch London

Nov 2017

A solution aiming for refugees. we developed an application to provide them with a more easy way to adapt to the unfamiliar nation. Within the application, the users can easily to know where to reach the information to help them settle down, it provides an online document storage feature as well. We have connected with the chief digital and information officer in Ministry of Justice to continue on developing the project.

# **Side Project**

## Attendance System UI

www.github.com/linuk/Attendance-UI

A web interface of an attendance system before the interview. It fetches the employee's daily logs of entering and leaving time from the database, calculates the average working hours within a month or a year, and shows the statics in the table or the line chart. It also provides search features to search specific data of the employee.

Technologies used: HTML5, SASS, CSS3, AJAX, jQuery, MySQL, PHP

## Other Information

- Tier 4 VISA
- References on request